# ALEXANDER VARGAS VILLAGOMEZ



### **Contact**

#### Address:

C/ Antonio Neumane C/Sin nombre Cuenca Ecuador

#### Phone:

(+593) 93 992 0808

#### Email:

 $a lexander\_9o@hotmail.com$ 

#### Linkedin:

**Alexander Vargas** 

#### Git Hub:

AlexVargasV

## Languages

Spanish – NATIVE English – B2 Japanese – N5

## Knowledge

PHP, Wordpress, WooComerce, MasterStudy, Python, Mysql, Tensorflow, NodeJS, Flutter, Reac, Amazon Web Service, DevOps, Django.

## **Summary**

Semi Senior Full Stack Web Developer specializing in PHP frameworks. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, PHP OOP, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL and other mobile languages as a Flutter and React Native. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

### **Skill Highlights**

- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Adaptability

- Responsability
- Innovative
- Leadearship

# **Experience**

Front-end Web Developer - 04/2019 to 09/2019 A2O Dev, Santa Cruz Bolivia Project Vetology AI

- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- Image recognition Scripts to validate data for AI application

AIESEC Global Volunteer - 10/2019 to 2/2020

Forza Laser, Quito Ecuador Project E- Learning Web page

I realized web test and devOps with amazon, also I contribute to build a
web application with NodeJS and react, and fixed bugs in e commerce
web with WordPress and WooCommerce plugin.

Al Developer - 11/2020 to 03/2021

Temuco University, Temuco, Chile Project atmospheric pollution

 I worked with mathematicians and electronic engineers to build a web application that receives many contamination parameters and the Neuronal networking evaluate that and give us a result with feedbacks and future result, the AI was built with TensorFlow.

Mobile Developer - 04/2021 to 12/2021

Military Engineering school, Santa Cruz-Bolivia

• Cooperate with designers and marketing are to create an application that informs about price, careers, service, events and give the best experience of the user, the application was create in flutter with Mysql Database.

Web Developer - 02/2022 to Current

Estudio XYX, Cuenca- Ecuador project CRM And E-Learning

• I collaborate to create a CRM that make an electronic billing with legal standards of Ecuador, also I worked with post-petition on amazon web services, this crm was built in Codelgniter 5.

### **Education**

University: **System Engineering** 2016-2020 (Finished) Bolivia-Santa Cruz Military Engineering school

Master: Artificial intelligence (Current) España- La rioja Rioja University (UNIR)